[{"answer": "I wanna have supper waitin'", "docId": "Braveheart.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "my friend, we'll get 'em", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Someone dead from this household", "docId": "Braveheart.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "What it means in that place", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "We'll sleep here tonight. You'll come home with me. We'll let the house, and the lands to", "docId": "Braveheart.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "Didn't want your father to die either, did ya? But it happened", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Sir, I know it was strange of me to invite my friend to ride last night. I assure you, I", "docId": "Braveheart.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "What kind of meeting", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "What happened", "docId": "Braveheart.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "What girl?", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "What girl?", "docId": "Braveheart.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "The girl on the horse! Stop her", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "You will embrace this rebellion. Support it, from our lands in the north. I will gain English favor by condemning it and ordering it opposed from our lands in the south. Whichever way the tide runs, we will rise", "docId": "Braveheart.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "You admire him. Uncompromising men are easy to admire. He has courage. So does a dog. But you must understand thi", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "Excellent! my friend is my name. I'm the most wanted man on the that place. Except I'm not on the that place of course, more's the pity", "docId": "Braveheart.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "A patriot", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Where is thy salute", "docId": "Braveheart.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "This is our army. To join it, you give homage", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "For presenting yourselves on this battlefield, I give you thanks", "docId": "Braveheart.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "I give homage to that place. And if this is your army, why does it go", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "I understand that you have recently been given the rank of knight", "docId": "Braveheart.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "Did God make you the sacker of peaceful cities? The executioner of the king's nephew, my husband's own cousin", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "A Lordship. And gold. That I should become my friend", "docId": "Braveheart.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "SLAVES ARE MADE IN SUCH WAYS", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "A thousand.  You have made me Guardian of that place. So I tell you this is what we face", "docId": "Braveheart.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "Peace?", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "Then tell me what a king is! Is he a man who believes only what others believe? Is he one who calculates the numbers for and against him but never weighs the strength in your own heart? There is strength in you. I see it. I know it", "docId": "Braveheart.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "And I will consult with mine", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "I am the one who is rotting. But I think your face looks graver than mine", "docId": "Braveheart.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "So more men were slaughtered uselessly", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "There will be a new shipment of supplies coming north next month. Food and weapons. They will trav", "docId": "Braveheart.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "Then why did you come", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "You understand. Consider, before you laugh and say no. You will never own a throne, though you deserve one. But just as the sun will rise tomorrow, some man will rule that place. And what if his veins ran not with the blood of that place, but with that of a true king", "docId": "Braveheart.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "No. But can you love me for the sake of all you loved and lost? Or simply love me... because I love you", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "If I pay homage to another's throne, then how am I a king", "docId": "Braveheart.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "The crown is that of that place. And that place is my friend", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "Nor I! I want to live! I want a home and children and peace. I've asked god for those things. But He's brought me this sword. And if He wills that I must lay it down to have what He wants for my country, then I'll do that too", "docId": "Braveheart.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "We've lived a dream together. A dream of freedom", "qsentId": 38}]